So then, at the end, he gave me a tiara.
A tiara. Can you believe it, Grandma?
Yukiya...
Was he trying to kiss me?
I know it's just a game,
but he wouldn't try to kiss someone
he doesn't like at all, right?
I mean...
If he were just doing this
to win at the game
even though he doesn't like me...
Like...
That would be gross, right?
Sorry, Grandma, I lit too much incense.
Oh boy
Well, I'm headed to school now.
See you later.
You know, though, Grandma...
Some of the sticky notes were
stuff that we already did...
Koi-Kyun
And if he kissed me...
What if that ended up being the mood?
What do I do then?
I Want to End This Love Game
Episode 4
My Childhood Friend Will Do Anything
Miku hasn't tried the game
on me at all today.
Not that that's too unusual.
Maybe that date was a mistake.
Did I creep her out?
There were kiss scenes and
stuff in that shoujo manga,
but that's way too much for me.
And then I passed out in the end.
I look so lame...
Miku was so small and soft.
Yukiya.
You scared me!
What?
Actually...
I've been meaning to ask you something.
Why did you have all those sticky notes?
Were you really about to kiss me?
What do you think of me?
Were you going to kiss me
as part of the game? Or...
because you like me?
Um...
What?
I just wanted to make sure,
about the Love Game...
Huh?
R-Right.
You know how we decided anything goes
if we're trying to get
the other person flustered?
Yeah?
By anything, uh...
H-How far were you thinking?
Er...
Wh-Why would she ask that now?
Is this part of the game?
Is she trying to shake me up?
Or did I freak her out on the date?
Maybe she wants to set some rules?
Anything means anything, right?
I guess there isn't a limit to how far.
Th-Then, then...
Would that include stuff
that people who are in love would do?
W-Well, of course.
I see.
You would do those kinds of things
with someone you don't love, huh?
Huh?!
Are you dumb?! That's...
Only because it's you.
No way I'd do that with anyone else.
Huh?
Does he mean...?
I'm playing the Love Game
with you, you know.
Isn't that the whole point of the game?
It's not about whether
we love each other or not.
The point of the game is
to tell each other that we do.
I-I know, but...
Did that get you?
So annoying!
Of course he'd say that!
This kid wouldn't give
a proper answer to anything!
And it isn't like this wuss even
has the guts to do much anyway!
How can he be all "sure,"
like he's all that!
Yukiya doesn't get to be so smug!
Well, sure.
It isn't that I think much
of you or anything...
So... I can do anything then,
for real?
Yeah, that's right.
That's what I just said.
For real real? Anything?
Yeah. Anything.
Maybe I'll just go ahead
and sleep on top of him.
"I'll have you for dessert today."
Uh-oh.
Are you having some naughty fantasies?
Huh?
What makes you think that?
Maybe you just think I am because
you're having skeevy thoughts.
When you say "anything"...
That includes doing stuff like this.
Obviously.
Yukiya...
You're clenching. Are you okay?
My strength must get your heart racing.
Look at you, acting so tough.
You can let go if you're
feeling shy, you know.
Right back at you.
What should we do after school?
Wanna stop by Mizter Donut?
Hey!
You didn't need to back off
in such a hurry.
Y-You must be stupid.
Well, I just won that wrestling match.
Wha?
You lost your balance,
so you obviously lost.
Also, we were never wrestling!
Is it all right if I touch you some more?
Okay. Sure.
Did you think I'd say that?!
You're such a pervert, Yukiya.
I said anything's fair,
and you went straight there.
So, that's that.
I won the game.
You're such a perv, Yukiya.
You're all red.
You're so easy.
Easy! Easy! Easy!
How am I supposed to
compete in the Love Game?!
I Want to End This Love Game
Miku, you free today?
Nacchan.
Wanna study for exams
with me after school?
Oh, uh, sure.
What's wrong? You seem down.
I didn't get to talk to Yukiya
much today either.
N-No we aren't!
Come on, you're trying
to be tough again.
You're just holding back
talking to him, aren't you?
Okay, I'll set up a reason
for you to talk to him!
Leave it to your big sis!
We're the same age.
No, it's fine. It's not like...
Asagi-kun!
Wait, Nacchan?!
N-Nacchan-san?
May I help you?
Yeah, actually...
So...
Oh! Why don't the three
of us study together?
Miku seems desperate
to talk to you, so...
Nacchan!
Huh? What was that?
Sorry! I couldn't think
of anything to say.
I told you it's fine!
You keep trying to be the big
sister and messing things up!
So, anyway, Nacchan wants
the three of us to study together.
Correct?
Y-Yes.
Maybe it's because of that dream,
but even the sounds of her
studying are getting to me.
Habits of a Successful Woman
~The Gate of Desires Opening in the Future~
That's good knowledge!
I'm gonna go find the rest.
What about studying for exams?
I don't know how her grades are so good.
Calm down!
We finally got confirmation
that anything goes!
Why do I have to be
so intimidated by Yukiya?
I just need to get him
before he gets me!
Just like with
chargers!
No one else can see us in this spot.
No one would know what we're doing!
This is the perfect stage where I can literally do anything!
I win.
There's nothing stopping me now.
Just watch what I...
What I'm capable of!
What I can do to you!
And then...
Ooh, I see...
Ooh...
I see...
One hour
later
I can't!
No way!
"Anything" means...
Wait, what does "anything" mean?
Actually, what is he going to do to me?
I have so many plans...
But now that anything goes,
I don't know what to do anymore.
We're studying.
Please enter quietly!
Sorry.
I just wanted to get my eraser.
N-Nah.
I dunno...
I'm finally here with Miku, and I don't
even know how to talk to her anymore.
Have we ever been
so silent together before?
If we can't even talk to each other
for the Love Game anymore,
we're really going to be...
Also, why isn't she trying
anything on me?
What's wrong?
Why is she making that face?
Is it because I said "anything goes"?
Is she afraid of what I might do?
Hey...
Wh-What?
You've been acting weird today.
You're thinking about me, aren't you?
H-Huh?
Obviously I'm not.
You don't need to worry.
I'm not going to do anything that weird.
What do you mean, "that weird"?
I mean, you know...
I won't do anything that you'd hate.
Oh?
Anything I'd hate? Like what?
Can we stop already?
Is it something you
can't even say out loud?
We're in the library.
Kindly be quiet, please.
Experiences of a Capable Woman
It's hard being
a successful woman!
Yukiya, there's somewhere I wanna go.
Mind coming with me later?
Well? Please?
I guess.
If it won't take much time.
Yay!
I see what's going on.
It's the after-school date!
I've been simulating the after-school
date in my mind every day during class.
Heart-pound
You're on. I accept this
Love Game challenge!
It only took a little cutesy begging.
Yukiya's such a simp.
He's been yanking around so much lately.
I'm going to remind him
who he's up against!
This is...
That notorious café known for
instantly vaporizing introverts!
Dammit... She's really going at it now!
She's using her home turf advantage!
Oh, right, introverts don't
like ordering at Starparty.
You gonna be okay, Yukiya?
Fool, this is nothing!
The reason being...
That I've been studying coffee beans
in anticipation of this day!
I endured that date.
Nothing scares me now!
Welcome.
May I take your order?
Um...
Frappe...?
Caramel Frappuccino
Matcha Cream Frappuccino
Vanilla Cream Frappuccino
Mango Passion Tea
Are these even drinks?
My coffee bean knowledge
doesn't even matter here!
Also, it's so expensive!
I only have 580 yen left over
after I splurged the other day.
The sandwiches look good too, but...
Teriyaki Green Sandwich                  Yen
Yen
Egg Salad Sandwich
You might like this one, Yukiya.
We have 9 varieties of
milk to choose from at
the same price!
Right.
I guess I could afford this.
This one, then.
Yes, sir.
Would you like it iced or hot?
Iced.
Okay, I'll have...
One grande Matcha Strawberry Frappe
with extra matcha powder,
and added chocolate chips
and chocolate sauce.
And then...
I like
your pigtails
What?
Does she actually eat this much?
You were so stiff, Yukiya.
I get it.
Coming to Starparty after school
with such a cute girl...
It's just a coffee shop.
It isn't any different
from boss's place.
Stare.
What?
Such. A. Cute. Girl.
Shush. I heard you. I'm ignoring you.
I like
your pigtails
It's so matcha-y!
Chiffon cakes are so spongy.
Yukiya, remember when
you saw earl gray cupcakes
and you asked,
"does this have pepper in it?"
She seems awful happy today.
It was ganache-flavored until recently.
Yeah?
Do you know what ganache is?
Of course I do!
Speaking of ganache,
I went to have cake with Akane
and Nacchan the other day...
Miku's grinning all the time.
And there was this ganache cake that
said it used chocolate from Hokkaido.
She's always going on about
trivial stuff with so much joy.
I like seeing her talking so happily.
So then, when I saw ganache,
I started craving it, and...
Man, I'm pretty full.
I bet.
I figured you could never finish it.
You can have it, Yukiya.
But you bought it for yourself.
It's yummy.
Eat it.
Wow!
Right? I knew you'd like that.
Did she...
I made him spend so much
money the other day.
I wanted to repay him, but this
guy never just accepts things.
He's such a pain.
You didn't need to bother.
It says something there.
Hm? This?
I like
your pigtails
What is this?
Who would write this?
The barista.
They write things once in a while.
What's wrong?
What is it?
I'm just cringing because it's so shallow.
It says something on yours, too.
You make a wonderful couple
Oh? Uh-huh.
I guess that's how people see us, huh?
People think we're a couple.
How do you feel about that?
What do you mean?
I don't mind.
Oh. Okay.
This legit makes me happy, though.
Maybe because it's hand-written.
It's a bit touching, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess.
Here.
It's beautiful when you go from
pouting to smiling.
Miku
It's beautiful when you go from
pouting to smiling.
Miku
It's beautiful when you go from
pouting to smiling.
Miku
Did your heart skip a beat?
Over what?
Over this piece of paper
that says "It's beautiful when
you go from pouting to smiling"?
Don't read it out loud!
Fine, I have one for you too, then.
What is this?
You can't tell?
It's you.
Huh? It's me?
You're so childlike,
yet you have the mind to hide
your hairband under your hair.
That's the essence of your pigtails.
It looks good on you, Miku.
Yukiya drew me.
Even though he can't draw.
Wait, did you seriously draw that
on the back of the receipt?!
I'm headed to the bathroom.
'Kay.
It's beautiful when you go from
pouting to smiling.
Miku
To be continued
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Comes In the Morning
Do you ever go to
the convenience store at night?
There's just something reassuring about
that glaring light in the night, right?
I think it's written in our DNA that
we should find comfort in the campfire.
Next episode: "My Childhood Friend
Comes In the Morning."